[
 {
   "No": 1,
   "Quiz question": "Who is the dictator of Cuba?",
   "Answer": "Fidel Castro"
 },
 {
   "No": 2,
   "Quiz question": "Who was the dictator of Iraq?",
   "Answer": "Saddam Hussain"
 },
 {
   "No": 3,
   "Quiz question": "In which state was George W Bush governor before becoming President of the United States?",
   "Answer": "Texas"
 },
 {
   "No": 4,
   "Quiz question": "In which state was Bill Clinton governor before becoming President of the United States?",
   "Answer": "Arkansas"
 },
 {
   "No": 5,
   "Quiz question": "In what year became John Major the leader of the Conservative Party?",
   "Answer": "In the year 1990"
 },
 {
   "No": 6,
   "Quiz question": "In what year was the Berlin wall built?",
   "Answer": "In the year 1961"
 },
 {
   "No": 7,
   "Quiz question": "Jozip Broz was formerly a Yugoslav marshal and statesman. He became prime minister in 1945 and president in 1953. Give a more familiar name.",
   "Answer": "Tito"
 },
 {
   "No": 8,
   "Quiz question": "In what year were women granted equal voting rights in the UK?",
   "Answer": "1928"
 },
 {
   "No": 9,
   "Quiz question": "Who was the Portuguese dictator at the time of Franco?",
   "Answer": "Salazar"
 },
 {
   "No": 10,
   "Quiz question": "What is the defoliant called that was used in Vietnam?",
   "Answer": "Agent Orange"
 },
 {
   "No": 11,
   "Quiz question": "What is the most spoken language in Belgium?",
   "Answer": "Dutch language"
 },
 {
   "No": 12,
   "Quiz question": "How many heads of presidents are carved into Mount Rushmore?",
   "Answer": "Four heads"
 },
 {
   "No": 13,
   "Quiz question": "For how many years is a French president elected?",
   "Answer": "Five years"
 },
 {
   "No": 14,
   "Quiz question": "Who is the only British Prime Minister to be murdered?",
   "Answer": "Spencer Percival"
 },
 {
   "No": 15,
   "Quiz question": "In which country happened the Orange Revolution between 2004-2005?",
   "Answer": "Ukraine"
 },
 {
   "No": 16,
   "Quiz question": "Which country had a Prime Minister and President who were twin brothers?",
   "Answer": "Poland"
 },
 {
   "No": 17,
   "Quiz question": "How many directly elected mayors does England have?",
   "Answer": "24"
 },
 {
   "No": 18,
   "Quiz question": "For which state did Arnold Schwarzenegger become governor in November 2003?",
   "Answer": "California"
 },
 {
   "No": 19,
   "Quiz question": "What date was the Good Friday Agreement signed on?",
   "Answer": "10 April 1998"
 },
 {
   "No": 20,
   "Quiz question": "What is the name of the country house given to the sitting Prime Minister of the UK?",
   "Answer": "Chequers Court"
 }
]
